(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T01:19:05.055070",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
バンダイ・バンダイスピリッツより
From Bandai and Bandai Spirits,
ホロライブEXPO 2025の会場にある特設ブースで、展示中の商品をご紹介！
we're introducing products on display at the special booth at hololive EXPO 2025!
ホロライブ エキスポ 2025限定の 一番くじ特設フォトブースも展開中！
Hololive Expo 2025 limited Ichiban Kuji special photo booth is also open!
モニターをタッチしてくじ券をめくり、 出たデザインと一緒に撮影できます。
Touch the monitor to draw a lottery ticket, and take a photo with the revealed design!
未知の期待 抱え 出会った あの日の僕らは
Carrying unknown expectations, we met on that day
The Last Frontier から なんと！フィギュア化決定！
From The Last Frontier, surprise! Figure adaptation announced!
あの感動をもう一度… 飛び立つ歌を
That emotion once more... a song to take flight
スケールフィギュア化決定！星街すいせい AZKi
Scale figures decided! Hoshimachi Suisei & AZKi
フリューから『ホロライブ』プライズが 全国アミューズメント施設にて続々展開中！
Furyu's Hololive prizes are rolling out across amusement facilities nationwide!
パペットぬいぐるみ
Puppet plushies
寝そべりぬいぐるみ
Sleeping plushies
指パペット
Finger puppets
キャンディ缶
Candy tins
4月からは新たにひっかけフィギュアも登場！
Hanging figures arriving in April!
FURYU PRIZE
台湾旅行中、最も便利な決済サービスを提供します。
Providing the most convenient payment service during your trip to Taiwan.
新商品まもなく登場！
New products coming soon!
hololive 6th fes. 一卡通限定盲包 第一弾 全20+1種 2025年夏 発売予定
hololive 6th fes. iPASS Limited Blind Pack Vol. 1, 20+1 types, Summer 2025
第二弾 全20+1種 2025年夏 発売予定
Vol. 2, 20+1 types, Summer 2025
第三弾 全20+1種 2025年夏 発売予定
Vol. 3, 20+1 types, Summer 2025
歌いたい曲が入っていなかった
The song you wanted to sing wasn't there?
だったらJOYSOUND X1で歌おうぜ！
Then let's sing on JOYSOUND X1!
曲数No.1
Song count No.1
AIが採点 絶賛
AI scoring, acclaimed
JOYSOUNDでボリュームに歌おう JOYSOUND X1
Sing your heart out on JOYSOUND, JOYSOUND X1
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony DAY1
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください 声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.
バンダイ バンダイスピリッツより
From Bandai and Bandai Spirits,
ホロライブエキスポ2025の会場にある
at the special booth at the Hololive Expo 2025 venue,
特設ブースで展示中の商品をご紹介！
we're introducing the products on display!
特設フォトブースも展開中！
Special photo booth also in deployment!
出てきたデザインと一緒に撮影できます！
You can take photos with the design that appears!
hololive 5th fes.で歌われた名曲
Songs sung at hololive 5th fes.
The Last Frontierからなんと！
"The Last Frontier" is getting...
フィギュア化決定！
made into figures!
あの感動をもう一度…
Relive that emotion once again...
フリューから『ホロライブ』プライズが全国アミューズメント施設に続々展開中！
FuRyu's "hololive" prizes are rolling out across amusement facilities nationwide!
4月からは新たにひっかけフィギュアも登場！
New dangling figures coming in April!
90人のhololive and HOLOSTARSタレントから好きな1人を選ぼう！
Pick your favorite from 90 hololive and HOLOSTARS talents!
レーザーを発射する秒1個マークを刻む秒針 レトロ宇宙空間のバトルをアリーナを文字盤にイメージしたデザイン
Laser-shooting plane marks each second. Retro space battle arena on your dial.
特殊ミッションアリーナ盤面上のミステリアスな透明ダイアル 透ける文字盤＆ダイアル エリート戦闘機がパワーアップするたびに細かく秒針が同期 紫外線ライトが暴く闇に潜む隠れモンスターが浮かび上がる！
Final mission arena on mysterious transparent dial. Elite fighter jet powering up with every tick. UV light reveals hidden monsters lurking in the shadows.
90人のプレイヤーからタレントから好きな1人を時計の裏側に！
Personalize with 90 players on transparent case back!
3月8日よりUNDONE.COMおよびUNDONE.CO.JPにて先行予約開始
PRE-ORDER NOW! Starts from 8 March at UNDONE.COM and UNDONE.CO.JP
台湾旅行中、最も便利な決済サービスを提供します。
Providing the most convenient payment service during your trip to Taiwan.
新商品まもなく登場！
New products coming soon!
hololive 6th fes. 一卡通限定盲包 第一弾 全20+1種 2025年夏 発売予定
hololive 6th fes. iPASS Limited Blind Pack Vol. 1 (20 + 1 types) releasing Summer 2025
hololive 6th fes. 一卡通限定盲包 第二弾 全20+1種 2025年夏 発売予定
hololive 6th fes. iPASS Limited Blind Pack Vol. 2 (20 + 1 types) releasing Summer 2025
hololive 6th fes. 一卡通限定盲包 第三弾 全20+1種 2025年夏 発売予定
hololive 6th fes. iPASS Limited Blind Pack Vol. 3 (20 + 1 types) releasing Summer 2025
歌いたい曲が入っていなかった だったらJOYSOUND X1で歌おうぜ
Couldn't find the song you wanted to sing? Let's sing it on JOYSOUND X1!
JOYSOUND X1 登場！
JOYSOUND X1 is now available!
曲数No. 1 AIが採点 絶賛
Most songs, No. 1. AI scoring is amazing!
KARAOKE 最高！最高！
KARAOKE is simply the best!
JOYSOUNDボリューム 歌いたい曲があるって最高
Having songs you want to sing is the best with JOYSOUND's high volume!
JOYSOUND X1
超特大ぬいぐるみブランド「どきゅーと」から商品化決定！
Ultra-large plush brand "DoQute" productization decided!
約100cmサイズぬいぐるみにと！
As plushies in approx. 100cm size!
2025年夏 受注開始予定
Pre-orders scheduled to start Summer 2025
タイトーブースにてサンプル展示中！詳細はタイト検索
Sample on display at Taito booths! Search Taito
グルーヴコースター最新作に白上フブキとさくらみこがキャラクターボイスで参戦！
Fubuki Shirakami and Miko Sakura star in character voices for Groove Coaster's latest!
人気曲や私たちが歌う曲も楽しめる！
Enjoy popular tracks and songs sung by us too!
シリーズ完全新作 GROOVE COASTER -FUTURE PERFORMERS- 2025年リリース予定 駆け抜けようミライのGrooveを！
Brand new series: GROOVE COASTER -FUTURE PERFORMERS-. Let's dash through the future's Groove in 2025!
コラボイベント実施中！ ホロライブ エキスポ コナミ
Collab events underway! Search hololive EXPO Konami
ゲームのオアシスに飛び込め！
Dive into the game oasis!
PalVerse フィギュア化決定！！
PalVerse figureization decided!
PalVerse Pale. フィギュア化決定！！
PalVerse Pale figureization decided!
白上フブキ・大神ミオ フィギュア化決定 3月8日(土) 予約開始！！
Fubuki Shirakami & Mio Ookami figure reservation starts March 8th (Sat)!
宝鐘マリン 1/7スケールフィギュア 締切間近
Marine Houshou 1/7 scale figure reservation closing soon!
SHIBUYA TSUTAYA書店 × Design COCO 新ブランド始動 [AXGRIT]
SHIBUYA TSUTAYA Bookstore x Design COCO new brand launch: AXGRIT
2020年11月「百年梅酒 ぺこらVer」誕生！
Nov 2020: Pekora Version 100-Year Plum Wine born!
2022年5月「大吟醸 雪夜月」ブロンズメダル獲得！
May 2022: Yuki-Yo-Zuki Daiginjo wins Bronze Medal!
2023年5月「雪夜月 Favorite Model」ブロンズメダル獲得！
May 2023: Yuki-Yo-Zuki Favorite Model wins Bronze Medal!
2024年12月「微発泡 雪夜月」誕生！
Dec 2024: Sparkling Yuki-Yo-Zuki born!
2022年4月「ノエルのポーション」誕生！
Apr 2022: Noel's Potion born!
2023年3月「酔いたい焼き さくらみこすぺしゃる」誕生！
Mar 2023: Sakura Miko's Special Yuitaiyaki Liquor born!
2024年10月「マリンズラム」誕生！
Oct 2024: Marine Rum born!
推しの夢叶えます。 明利酒類 Meiri.Co.,ltd
Granting your oshi's dreams. Meiri Shurui Co., Ltd.
特報
Special Report!
2025年夏 コラボカフェ・プライズ 開催決定 続報は公式XやHPをチェック！ (旧Twitter)
STREET FIGHTER 6 x hololive collaboration cafe & prizes coming Summer 2025! Check official X and HP for updates! (Formerly Twitter)
harmony 重ねた言葉 届け
Harmony — layered words, reach out,
たどたどしく 描いては
Clumsily drawing our dreams,
ぎこちないって笑ってた
Laughing at how awkward they seemed.
未来 予想 あの日の 続きを 見よう
Let’s continue the story we envisioned that day.
手と手 繋いで 風も着こなして
Hand in hand, embracing the wind,
扉を叩いて 連れてきてよ
Knock on doors — we’ll go together.
どんなことも きっと
No matter what comes our way,
一緒なら 叶えていける
If we’re together, we can make it happen.
【 la - la - la - la 】 鳴りやまない 希望の ベル ほら
The bell of hope keeps ringing — listen.
【 la - la - la - la 】 聞こえてる 歌 ah
Can you hear this song? Ah...
harmony 重ねた 言葉
Harmony — layered words
鮮やかな 日々の 向こう
Beyond the vivid days ahead,
ずっと君と彩るよ ストーリー
Always with you, we’ll color this story.
ハートに 結んだ 夢が
The dreams tied to our hearts
空へ 駆けてゆく
Race toward the sky,
キラメキに 乗せて
Carried on shimmering light —
あなたへ 届け
Let them reach you,
メロディー どこまでも ！
This melody — endlessly!
何気ない こと 思い出す
Recalling the little things,
一人じゃないよって 深呼吸
Taking a deep breath, knowing I’m not alone.
未体験 楽しむ 魔法の 言葉
Embracing the unknown — that’s the magic of words.
一息 ついて ふと 振り返って
Pausing for a moment, looking back,
また君を 知って その度に
Learning more about you each time,
ちょっと 勇気 出して
And with just a bit of courage,
明日へ 飛び込んで いける
I can dive into tomorrow.
【 la - la - la - la 】 降り積もる 道しるべ は まだ
The path ahead is still being laid —
【 la - la - la - la 】 覚えてる 歌 ah
Yet I remember this song, ah...
harmony 手を 伸ばしたら
Harmony — when I reach out,
足跡 に 虹が かかる
A rainbow forms over our footprints.
きっと 晴れる 口ずさむ ステージ
The sky will surely clear, humming on this stage,
ハートに 記した 場所へ
Guided by the marks on my heart,
運ぶ 約束を
A promise carries me forward,
輝きに 乗せて
Riding on its radiance,
世界へ 響け
Let it echo through the world —
メロディー いつまでも ！
This melody, forever!
【 la - la - la - la 】 君と踏み出した あの 一歩 あの 瞬間が
That first step we took together, that very moment
【 la - la - la - la 】 宝物だって 胸を張る 今
Is now a treasure I hold with pride.
【 la - la - la - la 】 歩いて話してはしゃいで 笑顔でゆくんだ
Walking, talking, playing, smiling — moving forward
【 la - la - la - la 】 色褪せないまま
Without fading away.
【 la - la - la - la 】 混ざり合う 僕らの声 ほら
Our voices blend together — listen,
【 la - la - la - la 】 聞こえてる 歌 ah
Can you hear this song? Ah...
harmony 重ねた 言葉
Harmony — layered words
鮮やかな 日々の 向こう
Beyond the vivid days ahead,
ずっと君と彩るよ ストーリー
Always with you, we’ll color this story.
ハートに 結んだ 夢が
The dreams tied to our hearts
空へ 駆け てゆく
Race toward the sky,
キラメキに 乗せて
Carried on shimmering light —
あなたへ 届け
Let them reach you.
hololive 6th fes. EXPO25_DAY1
[hololive 6th fes. EXPO25 DAY1]
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is ok.]
hololive 6th fes. Color Rice Harmony PENLIGHT COLORS
[hololive 6th fes. Penlight Colors]
harmony 重ねた 言葉 届け
harmony — layered words, reach out
たどたどしく 描いては
clumsily drawing our dreams
ぎこちないと 笑ってた
laughing at how awkward they seemed
未来 予想 あの日の続きを見よう
let’s continue the story we envisioned that day
手と手 繋いで 風も着こなして
hand in hand, embracing the wind
扉 叩いて 連れてきてよ
knocking on doors — we’ll go together
どんなこと も きっと
no matter what comes our way
一緒なら 叶えていける
if we’re together, we can make it happen
la - la - la - la
鳴りやまない 希望のベルほら
the bell of hope keeps ringing — listen
la - la - la - la
聞こえてる歌 ah
can you hear this song? ah…
harmony 重ねた 言葉
harmony — layered words
鮮やかな 日々の 向こう
beyond the vivid days ahead
ずっと君と彩るよストーリー
always with you, we’ll color this story
ハートに結んだ夢が
the dreams tied to our hearts
空へ駆けていく
race toward the sky
キラメキに乗せて
carried on shimmering light —
あなたへ届け
let them reach you
メロディー どこまでも！
this melody — endlessly !
何気ないこと思い出す
recalling the little things
一人じゃないよって深呼吸
taking a deep breath, knowing I’m not alone
未体験楽しむ魔法の言葉
embracing the unknown —
一息ついてふと振り返って
that’s the magic of words
また君を知ってその都度に
pausing for a moment, looking back
ちょっと勇気出して
learning more about you each time
明日へ飛び込んでいける
and with just a bit of courage I can dive into tomorrow
la - la - la - la
降り積もる道しるべはまだ
the path ahead is still being laid
la - la - la - la
覚えてる歌 ah
yet I remember this song, ah…
harmony 手を伸ばしたら
harmony — when I reach out
足跡に虹がかかる
a rainbow forms over our footprints
きっと晴れる口ずさむステージ
the sky will surely clear, humming on this stage
ハートに記した場所へ
guided by the marks on my heart
運ぶ約束を
a promise carries me forward
輝きに乗せて
riding on its radiance
世界へ響け
let it echo through the world —
メロディーいつまでも！
this melody, forever !
la - la - la - la
君と踏み出したあの最初あの瞬間が
that first step we took together, that very moment
la - la - la - la
宝物だって胸を張る今
is now a treasure I hold with pride
la - la - la - la
あるいいきてはなしてはしゃいでおえがいてゆくんだ
walking, talking, playing, smiling — moving forward without fading away
la - la - la - la
色褪せないまま
our voices blend together — listen
la - la - la - la
まざり合う僕らの声ほら
can you hear this song? ah…
la - la - la - la
聞こえてる歌 ah
harmony — layered words
harmony 重ねた 言葉
beyond the vivid days ahead
鮮やかな 日々の 向こう
always with you, we’ll color this story
ずっと君と彩るよストーリー
the dreams tied to our hearts
ハートに結んだ夢が
race toward the sky
星街すいせい
Hoshimachi Suisei
赤井はあと
Akai Haato
夏色まつり
Natsuiro Matsuri
不知火フレア
Shiranui Flare
白銀ノエル
Shirogane Noel
角巻わため
Tsunomaki Watame
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
姫森ルーナ
Himemori Luna
桃鈴ねね
Momosuzu Nene
ラプラス・ダークネス
La+ Darknesss
博衣こより
Hakui Koyori
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
Moona Hoshinova
クレイジー・オリー
Kureiji Ollie
カエラ・コヴァルスキア
Kaela Kovalskia
IRyS
シオリ・ノヴェラ
Shiori Novella
古石ビジュー
Koseki Bijou
ネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト
Nerissa Ravencroft
フワワ・アビスガード
Fuwawa Abyssgard
モココ・アビスガード
Mococo Abyssgard
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony
だって僕は星だから
Because I am a star,
ステラ ステラ
Stellar, stellar
きっと 君はもう気付いていた
I'm sure you had already noticed
僕の心の奥で砕いた
What was shattered deep in my heart
それがこれから話す陳腐なモノローグさ
A clichéd monologue I'll tell you from now on
ずっと言えない言葉があった
There were words I could never say
壊せない壁があったんだ ずっとさ
And walls I could never break through all along
ふっと香りのたつ朝の匂いが
The scent of morning wafting in the air
どうしようもなく憎らしくて
Was somehow so frustratingly hateful
部屋の隅で膝を抱えて震えていた
I sat in the corner of my room, hugging my knees and trembling
太陽なんていらないから
I don't need the sunshine
明けなまいでいて
Please don't let dawn break
その手を伸ばして 誰かに届くように
Reach out your hand so it can reach someone
その手を伸ばして
Extend that hand...
誰かに届くように
So it reaches someone
僕だって君と同じ 特別なんじゃなくて
I'm not special, just like you are
そうさ僕は夜を歌う stellar stellar
That's right, I sing to the night, stellar stellar
ありったけの輝きで今宵音楽はずっとずっと止まらない
With all my brilliance tonight, my music will never, ever stop
そうだ僕がずっとなりたかったのは
That's right, what I always wanted to be
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
Was never a waiting Cinderella,
迎えに行く王子様だ
But the prince going to greet her
だって僕は星だから
Because I am a star!
夜空を彩って 輝いて
Decorating the night sky, shining brightly
今音楽はずっとずっとやまない
Now music will never, ever stop
そうだ僕がずっと泣きたかったのは
That's right, what I always wanted to cry out
満天の星空の下じゃ
Beneath a starry night sky
何も言えない言葉があったんだ
There were words I couldn't say
こわれない壁があったんだ ずっとさ
And walls that wouldn't break, all along
ずっとありふれた話なんだ
It's always been a cliché story
理想だけ書き連ねていたノートの隅に眠る本能
An instinct sleeping in the margin of a notebook where I only wrote down ideals
わざなんだ、きっと
It was surely...
視界はまだ見えない
My vision is not yet clear,
未来はまだ知り得ない
The future cannot yet be known.
探した答えがいつか
The answer I searched for someday
生きてきた証になるんだ
Will become proof that I've lived.
走り続ける夜行バス
The night bus keeps running on,
希望に紡ぐ昨日へ
Toward yesterday spun with hope.
未開の夢に向かって
Heading toward undiscovered dreams,
僕らの旅は続いてく
Our journey continues onward.
星屑のように
Like stardust,
瞬くreflection
A twinkling reflection,
瞬間の光が僕らを
A fleeting light
探している
Is searching for us.
YOU&I
You & I,
もう何もかも
Throwing away
捨て去って
Everything now,
銀河の海の
At the edge of the galaxy's sea,
果てでいつか
Someday,
昨日へ逢いに行くんだ
I'll go to meet yesterday.
Eureka!!
さあ、何度でも君を見つけるよ
Come, no matter how many times, I'll find you.
止まった秒針が
The stopped clock hand
いま動き出す
Now starts to move
未来へと
Toward the future.
時代は巡り巡って
Eras turn and turn,
容易に消し去っていく
Easily erasing things away.
埋もれた昨日はいつか
Someday, buried yesterdays
なかったことにされて
Are treated as if they never happened.
流行廃れ掃き溜めてた
Fads discarded and swept aside,
希望を紡ぐ歌も
Even songs spinning hope
いつかを夢見てきっと
Dreaming of someday, surely
足掻いて彷徨っている
Struggling and wandering about.
愛想笑いで僕たちは
With polite smiles, we
誤魔化しながら生きてきた
Lived on while masking the truth.
傷付け合うことを怖がっては
Afraid of hurting one another,
逃げていた
We used to run away.
YOU&I
You & I,
もう何もかも
Throwing away
捨て去って
Everything now,
銀河の海の
At the edge of the galaxy's sea,
果てでいつか
Someday,
希望へ逢いに行くんだ
I'll go to meet hope.
Eureka!!
さあ、何度でもきっと
Come, surely, no matter how many times,
君を迎えに行くよ
I'll go to welcome you.
どんな遠くたってさ
No matter how far away,
必ず
Most certainly,
Most certainly.
harmony 重ねた言の葉 届け
Harmony of layered words, reach out,
たどたどしく描いては
Clumsily sketching out our dreams,
ぎこちないと笑ってた未来予想図
Smiling awkwardly at our future projections.
あの日の続きを見よう
Let's see the continuation of that day.
手と手繋いで風も着飾れて
Hand in hand, dressed up by the wind,
扉を叩いて連れてくよ
Knocking on doors, I'll take you along.
どんなこともきっと一緒なら叶えていける
Whatever happens, together we can make it real.
la-la-la-la
鳴りやまない希望のベル ほら
The bell of hope keeps ringing, look!
la-la-la-la
聞こえてる歌 ah
Can you hear this song, ah?
harmony 重ねた言の葉
Harmony of layered words,
鮮やかな日々の向こう
Beyond the vivid days,
ずっと君と彩るよストーリー
I'll always color this story with you.
ハートに結んだ夢が
The dreams tied to our hearts
空へ駆けてゆく
Race toward the sky.
キラメキに乗せてあなたへ届け
Borne on shimmering light, reach out to you,
メロディ どこまでも！
This melody, endlessly!
何気ないこと思い出す
Recalling the little things,
一人じゃないよって深呼吸
Taking a deep breath knowing I'm not alone.
未体験楽しむ魔法の言葉
Magic words to enjoy the unknown,
一息ついてふと振り返って
Taking a breath and looking back,
また君を知って
Getting to know you once more,
その都度ちょっと勇気出して
Gathering a bit of courage each time
明日へ飛び込んでいける
To dive right into tomorrow.
la-la-la-la
降り積もる道しるべはまだ
The path piled up with guideposts still
la-la-la-la
憶えている歌 ah
Remembers this song, ah.
harmony 手を伸ばしたら
Harmony, when we reach out our hands,
足跡に虹がかかる
A rainbow forms over our footprints.
きっと晴れる口ずさむステージ
Humming on this stage that will surely clear,
ハートに記した場所へ
To the place marked in our hearts,
運ぶ約束を
Carrying our promise.
輝きに乗せて世界へ響け
Riding on radiance, let it echo to the world,
メロディ いつまでも！
This melody, forever!
harmony 重ねた 言葉 届け
harmony — layered words, reach out
たどたどしく 描いては
clumsily drawing our dreams
ぎこちない と 笑っていた
laughing at how awkward they seemed
未来予想 あの日の続きを見よう
let’s continue the story we envisioned that day
手と手 繋いで 風も着こなして
hand in hand, embracing the wind
扉 叩いて 連れてきてよ
knocking on doors — we’ll go together
どんなことも きっと
no matter what comes our way
一緒なら 叶えていける
if we’re together, we can make it happen
ララララ
La la la la,
鳴りやまない 希望のベルほら
the bell of hope keeps ringing — listen!
ララララ
La la la la,
聞こえてる歌 ah
can you hear this song? ah...
harmony 重ねた 言葉
harmony — layered words
鮮やかな 日々の向こう
beyond the vivid days ahead
ずっと君と彩るストーリー
always with you, we’ll color this story
ハートに結んだ 夢が
the dreams tied to our hearts
空へ 駆け て ゆく
race toward the sky
キラメキ に 乗せて
carried on shimmering light —
あなたへ 届け
let them reach you,
メロディー どこまでも！
this melody — endlessly!
何気ない こと 思い出す
recalling the little things,
一人じゃないよって 深呼吸
taking a deep breath, knowing I’m not alone.
未体験 楽しむ 魔法 の 言葉
Embracing the unknown — that’s the magic of words.
一息 ついて ふと振り返って
Pausing for a moment, looking back,
また君を知って そのたびに
learning more about you each time.
ちょっと勇気 出して
And with just a bit of courage,
明日へ飛び込んでいける
I can dive into tomorrow.
ララララ
La la la la,
降り積もる 道しるべは まだ
the path ahead is still being laid.
ララララ
La la la la,
覚えてる歌 ah
Yet I remember this song, ah...
harmony 手を伸ばしたら
Harmony — when I reach out,
足跡に 虹 が かかる
a rainbow forms over our footprints.
きっと晴れる 口ずさむ ステージ
The sky will surely clear, humming on this stage,
ハート に 記した 場所 へ
guided by the marks on my heart.
運ぶ 約束 を
A promise carries me forward,
輝き に 乗せて
riding on its radiance.
世界へ響け
Let it echo through the world —
メロディー いつまでも！
this melody, forever!
ララララ
La la la la,
君と踏み出した あの 一歩 あの 瞬間 が
that first step we took together, that very moment
ララララ
La la la la,
宝物だって 胸を張る 今
is now a treasure I hold with pride.
ララララ
La la la la,
歩いて 話して はしゃいで 笑顔でゆくんだ
walking, talking, playing, smiling —
ララララ
La la la la,
色褪せないまま
moving forward without fading away.
ララララ
La la la la,
混ざり合う 僕らの声ほら
our voices blend together — listen!
ララララ
La la la la,
聞こえてる歌 ah
can you hear this song? ah...
ああ もう うざっせえんだって 現状に絶望
Ah, I'm so sick and tired of it, despairing at the status quo,
溜め込んだ 痛み ココロ で 絶叫
screaming from the heart with all the accumulated pain!
誰も知らない ドブネズミの歌
A rat's song that nobody knows—
騒いで聞かせましょう
let's make some noise and let them hear it!
okay now, listen up
it’s time for something new
it's gon ' get crazy wild
it's gon' get crazy wild,
so hold on to this tune
いいでしょうか？ 今宵 は 僕 の showtime
May I? Tonight is my showtime!
同調圧力に屈した皆さん ayo
To everyone who gave in to peer pressure, ayo—
they want a revolution?
ha, we’ll give it to 'em
take a stand now
my wish is your command
you want a party?
follow behind me
Follow behind me—
カオスへとご招待
welcome to chaos!
窮鼠は猫噛む 気をつけてな
A cornered rat bites a cat, so watch out!
rogue rat runaway
gotta get out of this place
昼夜逆転 反転世界
day and night inverted, a reversed world!
rogue rat runaway
i won’t stay in my own lane
翻弄しちゃうぜ 追いかけて
toying with you, catching up like the wind...
風のように 霞むように
Like fading mist...
we 'll vanish into the night
we'll vanish into the night!
誰も見ちいな い
Nobody is watching,
今に見 て なさい
just you wait and see!
僕は世間子の奴隷 「鼻つまみ者」
I'm society's outcast, a nuisance!
they run away
so far away
暴れまくれ
Go wild!
they say i 'm scum, a loser
They say I'm scum, a loser—
too bad, i 've heard it all before
too bad, I've heard it all before!
my music 's all i need
My music's all I need,
tell my truth through melodies
wordplay that makes your heart boom
start up the party
start up the party—
we gon ' get rowdy
we gon' get rowdy!
ノイズが邪魔をしても
Even if noise gets in the way,
隙は見せるな 食われちまうぞ
don't show an opening or you'll get eaten up!
rogue rat runaway
i will keep you on your feet
always keep you guessing
知らず知らず 秩序乱す
Unknowingly disrupting the order,
we 'll vanish into the night
we'll vanish into the night!
大丈夫だよ
It's going to be alright.
険しい感情 ぶっ潰せば 感情
Crush those harsh emotions, emotion!
ドクドク ドクドク 脈打つ波動
Thumping, thumping, a pulsing wave!
原子番号315番 コホリニウム より入魂
Atomic number 315, Koholinium, putting my soul into it!
これは幸せになる 最高のニュースだよ！
This is the best news to make you happy!
病み付きみんなちゃえばいいじゃん
Wouldn't it be great if everyone got hooked?
欲しいなら叫べばいいじゃん
If you want it, just shout it out!
大好きですかー？
Do you love it?
幸せですかー？
Are you happy?
愛すれば救われる
If you love, you'll be saved.
ああ なんて素敵な世界なんでしょう
Ah, what a wonderful world it is.
一粒のその瞳で見つめて 焦がれて 燃えて 抜けちゃって
Gaze with those eyes, burn, yearn, and break through!
明るい未来に カンパ～イ！
Cheers to a bright future!
天才 天才 天才
Genius, genius, genius!
ハチャメチャにすっごい
Incredibly chaotic!
外されてOK
It's okay to stand out!
神的ックスタイル
Divine c-style!
成功 成功 成功
Success, success, success!
今日は絶対に 幸あれ
Today, absolute happiness to you!
The Salvation!
人生とは 爆発だ！
Life is an explosion!
ポチッとピポパン やっぱりちょっとカッコつけ
Click, beep, bang, trying to look cool after all!
計算通りよ 計算通りよ
Just as planned, just as planned!
チッケト チッケト...
Ticket, ticket...
実験だ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment!
チッケルダ！チッケルダ！
Get a ticket!
少年少女前を向け
Boys and girls, look ahead!
揺るぐ炎天さえたぶん希望論だって
Even the wavering blazing heat is just optimism,
ツレモドセ ツレモドセ
bring it back, bring it back!
三日月が赤く燃え上がる
As the crescent moon burns bright red.
さあさあ、コードを0で刻め
Come on, carve the code at zero.
想像力の外側の世界へ
To the world outside the imagination,
白いイヤホンを耳に当て
Placing white earphones to my ears,
少しニヤッとして合図する
I smile slightly and give the signal.
染み込んだこの温度が
This soaked-in temperature
ドアをノックした瞬間に溢れそうになるよ
is about to overflow the moment it knocks on the door.
「まだ見えない?」
"Still can't see it?"
目を凝らして臨む争奪戦
Straining my eyes to face the scramble.
あの日焦燥した脳裏から
From that day's impatient mind,
「今だ、取り戻せ」とコードが鳴り出しそうになる
the code seems to ring out, "Now, take it back."
愛しくて、辛くて、
So beloved, so painful,
世界を嫌ったヒトの
of people who hated the world,
酷く理不尽な「構成」
this terribly unreasonable "structure."
肯定してちゃ未来は生み出せない
If we just accept it, we can't create a future.
少年少女前を向け
Boys and girls, look ahead!
揺るぐ炎天さえたぶん希望論だって
Even the wavering blazing heat is just optimism,
ツレモドセ ツレモドセ
bring it back, bring it back!
三日月が赤く燃え上がる
As the crescent moon burns bright red.
さあさあ、コードを0で刻め
Come on, carve the code at zero.
想像力の外側の世界へ
To the world outside the imagination,
オーバーな空想戦線へ
to the over-the-top fantasy battlefront.
「お先にどうぞ」って舌を出す
"After you," I stick out my tongue
余裕ぶった無邪気な目
with an innocent, composed look.
「ほら出番だ」パスワードで
"Now it's your turn," with the password
目を覚ましたじゃじゃ馬は止まらない
the awakened wild horse won't stop.
もう夜が深くなる
The night is getting deeper now,
「オコサマ」なら燃える延長戦
for "kids," a burning overtime match.
逆境ぐあいがおクールだろ?
Isn't this adversity pretty cool?
眠れないね、まだまだ。
We can't sleep yet, not yet.
ほら早く!早く!!
Come on, hurry! Hurry!!
イン・テンポで視線を合わせて
Align our gazes in in-tempo,
ハイタッチでビートが鳴り出せば
when high-fives make the beat ring out,
考えてちゃ遅いでしょう?
thinking about it is too late, right?
ほら乗っかってこうぜ
Come on, let's ride along with it!
ワンコードで視線を合わせて
Align our gazes with one chord,
ぶっ飛んだグルーヴが渦巻けば
if a blown-away groove swirls around,
冗談じゃないみえるはずさ
it's no joke, you should be able to see it
そのハイエンドの景色の隙間に
in the gaps of that high-end scenery.
暗号チップの言葉も
Even the words of the encryption chip
合言葉だって言い合える
can be exchanged as our watchword.
少しだけ前を向ける
We can look ahead just a little bit,
少年少女前を向け
Boys and girls, look ahead!
揺るぐ炎天さえたぶん希望論だって
Even the wavering blazing heat is just optimism,
ツレモドセ ツレモドセ
bring it back, bring it back!
三日月が赤く燃え上がる
As the crescent moon burns bright red.
さあさあ、コードを0で刻め
Come on, carve the code at zero.
想像力の外側の世界へ
To the world outside the imagination,
オーバーな空想戦線へ
to the over-the-top fantasy battlefront.
掴み取れ 掴み取れ
Grasp it, grasp it!
たとえ太陽が赤く燃え盛ろうとも
Even if the sun burns fiercely red,
コードゼロで刻め その目を見開いた
carve the code at zero with wide-open eyes.
オーバーの妄想戦線 感情性能のメビウスの先へ
Beyond the Möbius strip of emotional performance on the exaggerated delusion battlefront.
セカイデ!
In the world!
前に前に前に 走れ運命よ
Run forward, run forward, run forward, chase your destiny!
次々 向かい風くぐり抜ける
Passing through the headwind one after another,
ゆらゆら 燃え上がる 魂で
With a soul swaying and blazing high,
もっと…
More...
勝利の雄叫び 1 2 Hi!
The battle cry of victory, 1, 2, high!
金色になりなびく 立て髪が
My golden-waving mane
僕の仲間 光らせてくんだ
Illuminates my comrades.
青くゆらめく 時の炎が
The blue-flickering flames of time
赤い情熱 照らせてくんだ
Illuminating my red passion.
電光石火 正面突破
Lightning-fast, frontal breakthrough,
どんな扉も ぶち破る
Smashing through any door,
日進月歩 百花繚乱
Progressing day by day, a riot of flowers.
前に前に前に 走れ運命よ
Run forward, run forward, run forward, chase your destiny!
次々 向かい風くぐり抜ける
Passing through the headwind one after another,
ゆらゆら 燃え上がる 魂で
With a soul swaying and blazing high,
もっと…
More...
勝利の雄叫び 1 2 Hi!
The battle cry of victory, 1, 2, high!
銀色に染まる この剣が
This silver-dyed sword
僕の敵を 黙らせてくんだ
Silences my enemies.
淡い夢のかけらの1つが
One piece of a faint dream
確かな今のかけ橋なんだ
Is the sure bridge to the present.
順風満帆 天真爛漫
Smooth sailing, innocent and carefree,
甘い罠には気をつけろ
Beware of sweet traps,
切磋琢磨 さっさ行こうさ
Work hard together, let's go right away!
前に前に前に 走れ運命よ
Run forward, run forward, run forward, chase your destiny!
次々 向かい風くぐり抜ける
Passing through the headwind one after another,
ゆらゆら 燃え上がる 魂で
With a soul swaying and blazing high,
もっと…
More...
勝利の雄叫び 1 2 Hi!
The battle cry of victory, 1, 2, high!
殺風景な景色だって
Even if the scenery is bleak,
みんな声 音色になって
Everyone's voices become timbres,
鮮やかに その未来の光を 掴んだれ!
Vividly seizing the light of that future!
不安ななんかないぜ
There's no anxiety,
罵声なんて蹴り飛ばせ
Kick away the jeers and insults,
Oh Yeah! 盛り上がれ!
Oh yeah! Get hyped up!
ぶるんぶるん 震え上がる使命に
To the mission shaking with a rumble,
しゅりゅんしゅりゅん 竜巻を巻き起こす
Stirring up a swirling tornado,
ざわざわ 山と海抱きしめて
Embracing the mountains and the sea,
もっと..
More...
前に前に前に 走れ運命よ
Run forward, run forward, run forward, chase your destiny!
次々 向かい風くぐり抜ける
Passing through the headwind one after another,
ゆらゆら 燃え上がる 魂で
With a soul swaying and blazing high,
もっと..
More...
勝利の雄叫び 1 2 Hi!
The battle cry of victory, 1, 2, high!
言いたいことがあるんだよ！
There is something I want to say!
やっぱり〇〇はかわいい！
After all, you're so cute!
すき好き大好き やばい！
I like you, love you, crazy about you!
言いたいことがあるんだよ！
There is something I want to say!
やっぱり〇〇はかわいい！
After all, you're so cute!
やっと見つけたお姫様
The princess I finally found
生まれ変わっても一緒だよ
Even if we're reborn, we'll be together
お前が変わっちまったって
Even if you change
一途に愛し続けるよ
I'll keep loving you devotedly
前に前に前に 走れ運命よ
Run forward, run forward, run forward, chase your destiny!
次々 向かい風くぐり抜ける
Passing through the headwind one after another,
ゆらゆら 燃え上がる 魂で
With a soul swaying and blazing high,
もっと..
More...
勝利の雄叫び 1 2 Hi!
The battle cry of victory, 1, 2, high!
勝利の雄叫び
The battle cry of victory,
勝利の雄叫び 1 2 Hi!
The battle cry of victory, 1, 2, high!
すごかったね。
That was amazing, right?
ホールすごかったよ。
The hall was amazing!
すごいよね。
It really was.
我が輩の方すごいけどね。
Though mine was even more amazing!
ぱ、ぱ、ぱ、ぱ、ぱ、我が輩は？
M-M-M-M-Mine was...
フレッ！フレッ！
Yay! Yay!
まっすぐどこまで、どこまで、どこまで〜って感じだよね。
It felt like going straight on and on!
なんてオタクに言わせない。
Don't make the otaku say stuff like that!
我が輩が言わせないように似合うから。
I won't let them, 'cause it suits me!
もね、つかれちゃった。
Man, I'm exhausted.
頑張ったから。頑張ったから。
'Cause I worked hard. I worked hard.
我が輩が一番好きなんこれ？
Is this what you like best, La+?
あ、ちょっと、自己紹介。
Ah, wait, self-introduction.
じゃ、先輩から。
Well then, seniors first.
はい！じゃあみんなオレンジ色を見せてくれるかなー？
Yes! Can everyone show me your orange lights?
おー！オレンジ！
Oh! Orange!
ありがとう！すごい！
Thank you! Amazing!
めっちゃあっちまでオレンジ！
Orange all the way over there!
すごいな。いいね。
That's incredible. Nice.
はいみんな！ホロライブのセーストハート、みんなのアイドル！夏色祭り！祭りです！
Yes everyone! Hololive's sweetest heart, everyone's idol! Natsuiro Matsuri! It's Matsuri!
ちょっと祭りやりたいことあるんでついでにやっていいですか？
There's something I wanna do at the festival, can I do it now?
お、なに？なに？
Oh, what? What?
今からのお祭りが「夏色祭りは清楚だよな？」って聞くんで、
Starting now, the festival is going to ask, "Natsuiro Matsuri is pure, right?"
あの、清楚だと思っては反応してください！
So if you think I'm pure, please react!
行くよ？行くよ？
Ready? Ready?
うん。
Yeah.
夏色祭りは！清楚だよなーっ！
Natsuiro Matsuri is... pure!
聞こえてない、聞こえてないセリフもあるか。
Did they not hear me? Or maybe some didn't hear.
ねねち、ねねち、ねねち。
Nenechi, Nenechi, Nenechi.
ねねち、なんか気まずいな。
Nenechi, this feels a bit awkward.
あの、顔に免じてください。
Um, please forgive me for my face's sake.
どうします？
What should we do?
みんな、そのままオレンジで大丈夫いでーす！いえーい！
Everyone, it's totally fine to stay orange! Yay!
みんなねねが、みんなの心のって言ったら、「エナジードリンク！」で返してね。
When Nene says "everyone's heart...", reply with "Energy Drink!"
みん、あ、ホロライブ爆誕ネプらぶのね！みんなの心のー？
Min-, ah, Hololive's newly born Neplove's! Everyone's heart is...?
エナジードリンク！ありがとー！
Energy Drink! Thank you!
もだすねねでーす！きょうよろしくー！
It's Modasu Nene! Nice to meet you today!
本当に同じ観客ですか？さっきと。
Is this really the same audience as before?
うん、同じだよねみんな。全然勢量が。
Yeah, it's the same, everyone. Totally different volume.
そう、なんかネネに優しいー。
Yeah, somehow they're so kind to Nene.
もすまん、まーん！
Mosuman, man!
ほらじゃあオレンジじゃないやつ行けよ。
Come on, then let's go with the non-orange ones.
じゃあオレンジじゃないやつ。
Now for the non-orange ones.
じゃあいつものよろしく！
Then, the usual! Let's go!
貴様ら！覚悟をせいよ！
You scumbags! Prepare yourselves!
イエス、マインロード！
Yes, my lord!
ありがとう、ありがとう！
Thank you, thank you!
我が輩の名前はラプラス・ダークネスー！
My name is La+ Darknesss!
すいちゃんから始まって、
Starting from Suichan,
我が輩もできましたけど！はい！
we managed to do it too! Yes!
はい。はい。
Yes. Yes.
やめて先輩、先輩！楽しくなっちゃってね！
Stop it, senpai, senpai! It got too fun!
じゃあ、ちなみに、２人は何言ったんですか？ネネチ何言ったの？
By the way, what did you two say? Nenechi, what did you say?
え、ねねは新しい曲を歌うんだけど、サンタツイ...あ、Xくんで、
Um, Nene is going to sing a new song, but on Santa-tsui... ah, on X,
ポストしたからみんなさすがに覚えて聞いてくれたよね！ね！
I posted about it, so everyone surely remembered and listened, right? Right?
えのー！
E-no!
今日我が輩と祭りさすがに覚えてなかったら処刑だからな！
Today, if you guys didn't remember me and Matsuri, it's execution!
だってね、あのもうコール完璧だと思うんだよね。
'Cause you know, I think the call is already 100% perfect.
ね、コール完璧。
Right, 100% call.
完璧だよ。
It was perfect.
お願いしますよ。
Please do your best.
完璧だよね？完璧だよね？
It was perfect, right? Perfect, right?
ほら、最前列の海外に怪我さ、ほらもう「イエーイ」って言ってくれてるよ！
Look, the foreigners in the front row are like, "Yay!", shouting for us!
すっごいわかりやすい。ねっこわかりやすいね。
Super easy to understand. Nekko is easy to understand, right?
ネッコ発見！ネッコ発見！
Nekko spotted! Nekko spotted!
抜いてこ、抜いてこ！
Let's pick them out, let's pick them out!
え、まつりは？あのー、内緒。
Eh, what about Matsuri? Um... it's a secret.
え！？
Eh?!
内緒？で、も、内緒？
A secret? But, a secret?
あの、オリジナル曲で、今までにない感じの、え、曲。
Um, with an original song, a feeling never seen before, um, a song.
内緒。え！？内緒？
Secret. Eh?! Secret?
今までにない？そう、でも、今日ね、お祭りすの、おんな祭りの子も来てると思うんですけど、
Never before? Yeah, but today, y'know, girls from the festival are also here, I think,
いるよね？うん。
aren't they? Yeah.
だからね、その子がちょっと共感できるような感じか。
So, that kid might be able to relate to it.
あ、も？あ、わかんない。どうなんだろうな。
Ah, mo? Ah, I don't know. I wonder how it is.
女の子祭りす。共感できる。
Girls' festival. Relatable.
ちなみに、ラプチは？みなさん、なんと我がハイ、何に？
By the way, what about Lapuchi? Everyone, what is my—what to?
この後歌いまーす！
I'll sing after this!
この後ー！？
After thisー!?
えー！？知らなかったー！知らなかったー！
Eh?! I didn't know! I didn't know!
リハーサル見させてくれたじゃん！
You let us watch the rehearsal!
じゃあ次は歌うんですけども、盛り上げてほしいね。
We're going to sing next, so we want you to get hyped up!
みんな盛り上げてほしい！
Everyone, get hyped up!
いっぱい、もっと声出せますか！？
Can you give us even more of your voices?!
イヤー！！
Yeah!!
ありがとうね。
Thank you!
そして、はい。ええとなんですのですが、あ、はい。あ、なんですのですが、わ。
And, yes. Um, well, ah, yes. Um, well, wow.
ここで！なんと無料パートが終わりますー！
Here! The free part is ending!
ま、でもね、あの、みんなラプ様の歌聞きたいと思うから、
Well, but you know, everyone wants to hear La+-sama's song,
ちゃんと見てくれたと思います。
so I think you watched it properly.
そしてですね、え、ハッシュタグ「#hololiveFesEXPO25_Day1」で、
And also, with the hashtag "#hololiveFesEXPO25_Day1",
ツイート、ポスト、お願いします！
please tweet and post!
はい、というわけで、本当に本当に無料パートここまでになります！
So, the free part really, really ends right here!
概要欄からチケットのご購入は、よろしくお願いします！
Please purchase your tickets from the description link!
もちろん我がはいだけじゃなくて、この後も、めっっちゃこの2人も含めてね、
Of course, not just myself, but from here on too, extremely including these two,
そうだよ！ホロメンがみんな頑張って歌って踊るので、よろしくねー！
That's right! All the holoments will do their best singing and dancing, so please look forward to it!
そして、我々最初のMCパートということでね。
And as our first MC part, you know.
今後、ちょっと恒例になる「アイズ」っていうのをみんなにもやってもらおうかなと思ってて。
From now on, we were thinking of having everyone do "Aizu", which is becoming a bit of a staple.
じゃあ、祭りさんが「せーの」って言ったら、みんなで「カラーライズハーモニー！」って言ってください！
So, when Matsuri-san says "Ready, set", everyone please say "Color Rise Harmony!"
いくよー！
Here we go!
せーの！カラーライズハーモニー！
Ready, set! Color Rise Harmony!
harmony 重ねた 言葉 届け
harmony — layered words, reach out
たどたどしく 描いて は
clumsily drawing our dreams
ぎこちない と 笑っ て た
laughing at how awkward they seemed
未来 予想 あの日 の 続き を 見 よう
let’s continue the story we envisioned that day
手と手 繋い で 風 も 着こなし て
hand in hand, embracing the wind
扉 叩い て 連れ て き て
knock on doors — we’ll go together
どんな こと も きっと
no matter what comes our way
一緒 なら 叶え て いける
if we’re together, we can make it happen
【 la - la - la - la 】
[ la - la - la - la ]
鳴りやま ない 希望 の ベル ほら
the bell of hope keeps ringing — listen
聞こえ て いる 歌 ah
can you hear this song? ah…
harmony 重ね た 言葉
harmony — layered words
鮮やか な 日々 の 向こう
beyond the vivid days ahead
ずっと 君 と 彩る よ ストーリー
always with you, we’ll color this story
ハート に 結ん だ 夢 が
the dreams tied to our hearts
空 へ 駆け て ゆく
race toward the sky
キラメキ に 乗せ て
carried on shimmering light —
あなたへ 届け
let them reach you
メロディー どこまでも !
this melody — endlessly!
何気ない こと 思い出す
recalling the little things
一人 じゃ ない よっ て 深呼吸
taking a deep breath, knowing I’m not alone
未体験 楽しむ 魔法 の 言葉
embracing the unknown — that’s the magic of words
一息 つい て ふと 振り返っ て
pausing for a moment, looking back
また 君 を 知っ て その たび に
learning more about you each time
ちょっと 勇気 出し て
and with just a bit of courage
明日へ 飛び込ん で いける
I can dive into tomorrow
【 la - la - la - la 】
[ la - la - la - la ]
降り積もる 道しるべ は まだ
the path ahead is still being laid
覚え て いる 歌 ah
yet I remember this song, ah…
harmony 手 を 伸ばし たら
harmony — when I reach out
足跡 に 虹 が かかる
a rainbow forms over our footprints
きっと 晴れる 口ずさむ ステージ
the sky will surely clear, humming on this stage
ハート に 記し た 場所 へ
guided by the marks on my heart
運ぶ 約束 を
a promise carries me forward
輝き に 乗せ て
riding on its radiance
世界 へ 響け
let it echo through the world —
メロディー いつまでも !
this melody, forever!
【 la - la - la - la 】
[ la - la - la - la ]
君 と 踏み出し た あの 一歩 あの 瞬間 が
that first step we took together, that very moment
【 la - la - la - la 】
[ la - la - la - la ]
宝物 だって 胸 を 張る 今
is now a treasure I hold with pride
【 la - la - la - la 】
[ la - la - la - la ]
歩い て 話し て はしゃい で 笑顔 で ゆく ん だ
walking, talking, playing, smiling — moving forward
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.